Guide to the Wayne P. Ellis Collection of Kodakiana, 1886-1989 and undated
Wayne P. Ellis Collection of Kodakiana 1886-1989 and undated
- Marketing Samples and Promotional Materials Series, [189-?]-[198-?] and undated
  - Contents of Box: (Box 88)
    - Novelties
      Wide variety of Kodak promotional materials used as giveaways and for in-store use. Almost all have no date, but most are 20th century artifacts.
      - Stuffed kangaroo with Pocket Kodak in pouch
      - Counter mat
      - Pocket Instamatic matchboxes, various matchbooks
      - Kodak "facts" playing cards
      - Negative pencil, Kodak pen
      - Kodaslide noise-making postcard
      - Kodak Park postcard
      - "Photographic oracle"
      - Processing/calendar cards
      - Kalart sunlight guide for taking pictures
      - Ads/instructions for Kodak Bank
      - Pocket coin bank
      - Kodak coin
      - Instamatic mini-notebook
      - "Filmsbee" (frisbee with film)
      - Magnifying glass
      - 65th anniversary buttons
      - Kodak pin
      - French calendar, 1973
      - French paperweight
      - "German Schnapps Novelty" (for New Year's?)
      - Kodak T-shirt
      - Calendar holder
      - Kodak medal
      - Kodak lighter
      - Kodak keychains
      - Kodak puzzle pieces
      - Filter test chart
      - Ma-Time Computer
      - Kodak Banner
      - Kodak reflector
      - "Brownies in Stock!" stamp
- Oversize Materials, circa 1918-1988 and undated
  Chiefly photographs used by Kodak for promotional campaigns, but also includes counter signs and some company history materials, including employee photographs.
  - Contents of Box: (Box 89)
    - Promotional materials, 1931-1978 and undated, (4 folders)
      Includes advertisement samples, sample scripts for demos, and some foreign advertising materials.
  - Contents of Box: (Box 90)
    - Framed black and white photograph - "No. 4 Panorama," undated
    - Unframed black and white photographs - includes Kodak girl, Velox display, undated
  - Contents of Box: (Box 91)
    - Framed photograph - Kodak girl, undated
  - Contents of Box: (Box 92)
    - Promotional materials, store-printed, ca. 1920, (22 items)
  - Contents of Box: (Box 93)
    - Kodak employee photographs, circa 1918-ca. 1924, (3 items)
    - Biographical information about George Eastman, 1954, 1976, 1988, (3 items)
  - Early Kodak advertisements scrapbook 1, 1880s-1912 (Box 94)
    [Contents digitized in the Emergence of Advertising in America online collection, numbers K0525-K0565.]
  - Early Kodak advertisements scrapbook 1, 1905-1919 (Box 95)
    [Contents digitized in the Emergence of Advertising in America online collection, numbers K0566-K0579.]